cheki.co.ke 2011-12-31

# Privacy Statement - Cheki.co.ke Buy and sell cars for sale, motorbikes, matatus and trucks for sale in Nairobi, Mombasa and Kenya. Used Toyota, Nissan, Subaru, Isuzu, BMW, Japanese and imported cars bikes trucks and more

## Search

Only display ads with prices

Only display ads with photos

| 

## Privacy Statement

 **CHEKI's commitment to maintaining your privacy**

CHEKI's values our users and recognise their right to keep personal information private. This statement discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for all sites managed by CHEKI.

 **Collecting information on CHEKI visitors**

CHEKI collects information on our site visitors collectively including which sections of the site are most frequently visited, how often and for how long. We use session cookies to identify you as a current user and these are alive only for the duration of your browser session. If you disable or reject session cookies you may not be able to access and use all features of our sites. You may adjust your browser settings to disable cookies being stored on your hard drive, however this may impact your user experience.

When visiting our web site, the site server makes a record of the visit and logs the following information for statistical and administrative purposes:

  * the user's server address 
  * the date and time of the visit to the site 
  * pages accessed and documents downloaded 
  * duration of the visit 
  * the type of browser used 
  * the previous site visited 
  * users location 

CHEKI utilises this information to improve and enhance our services by monitoring the areas on the site which are most popular to you. 

This information is not specific to an individual. While anonymous information does not tell us anything about the user specifically, it does tell how they used our site. This policy only covers the use of cookies by us. No attempt will be made to identify users or their browsing activities unless legally compelled to do so, such as in the event of an investigation, where a law enforcement agency may exercise a warrant to inspect log files.

 **Collecting information on CHEKI Members**

As part of registering for Email or SMS alerts with CHEKI, we collect personal contact information from you in order for you to receive alerts. 

We will only use this information to send you alerts of new advertisements on the CHEKI website that meets your preferences or to alert you to new products and services on the Cheki website or to alert you to potential fraud, security matter or false advertising if we detect it. 

Email Alerts and SMS Alerts are an optional service. CHEKI requests that you provide information relating to your preferences as well as your email address or SMS number so that we may notify you via email or SMS of new vehicles specific to your needs. Users can modify or delete their alert profiles online via [Email Alerts Unsubscribe](http://www.cheki.co.ke/email-unsubscribe) or [SMS Alerts Unsubscribe](http://www.cheki.co.ke/sms-unsubscribe). If you are having any problems, you can contact us directly at [info@cheki.co.ke](mailto:info@cheki.co.ke)

 **Contacting Sellers**

Making an online Contact Seller Request to an advertisement on CHEKI is a free and optional service that does not require registration. 

Contact Seller Requests require you to complete mandatory fields (name, phone and email) so that the advertiser can identify and contact you. These details are forwarded directly on to the third party advertiser. 

By submitting a Contact Seller form on CHEKI you are requesting that CHEKI pass the information to the Advertiser.

**CHEKI Partners & Advertisers**

CHEKI provides links and passes online applications to third party sites. The use of your information by these third party sites is not within the control of CHEKI and we cannot accept responsibility for the conduct of these companies. 

You may also directly contact advertisers to request access to any personal information that you have sent as part of an application.

 **Transborder data flows**

Sometimes, we transfer information to persons outside Kenya (e.g. I.T. contractors located in other parts of the world who provides us with services). 

By giving us your personal information, you consent to such disclosures. 

In addition, we believe that the recipients of such information are subject to a law, binding scheme or contract which effectively upholds principles for fair handling of the information that are substantially similar to Cheki’s Privacy Principles. 

**Feedback**

CHEKI welcomes ideas and feedback about all aspects of the site. CHEKI stores feedback that users send to us. This feedback will be used to administer and refine the service and may be shared with CHEKI partners either in aggregate form or with specific identifying characteristics removed. 

**Privacy & Site Changes**

From time to time, CHEKI may review and update its privacy statement. 

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with CHEKI, you can [contact us online](http://www.cheki.co.ke/contact) or at [info@cheki.co.ke](mailto:info@cheki.co.ke)
